Per G. Stensland Papers
Per G. Stensland Papers
- Speeches
  - Adult education, 1944-1957 (Box 10)
  - Adult education, undated (Box 10)
  - Community development, 1950-1963 (Box 11)
  - Community development, 1964-1966 (Box 11)
  - Educational sociology, 1960-1964 (Box 11)
  - Educational sociology, 1965-1971 (Box 11)
  - General, 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Continuing education, 1941-1942 (Box 11)
  - "America and Americans," and other early speeches, 1941-1948 (Box 11)
  - Clipping re speeches (Box 11)
  - Scrap book, Lubbock, Texas (Box 12)
  - Dissertation: John V. Gregory, 1956 (Box 12)
- Miscellaneous
  - Table (matrix) related to project or seminar planning, (approx. 4' x 3.5') (Box 12)
    See also Milbank Memorial Fund: Conferences and Seminars: Gantt charts related to seminar planning